<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[New Hope Church - Greenwood, IN]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[New Hope Church - Greenwood, IN]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/becomehope/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 19:48:15 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/becomehope/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>BECOME: Biblically Equipped Community On Mission Everywhere New Hope Church seeks to BECOME a Biblically Equipped Community On Mission Everywhere:  Biblically Equipped  We want to be in meaningful relationship with God, maturing in our faith each and every day. That is why we provide opportunities to BECOME biblically equipped through our Sunday morning teaching, Sunday adult classes, Hope Groups, age-graded ministries, and various training opportunities. "Love the Lord your God with all your heart and with all your soul and with all your mind and with all your strength." (Mark 12:30)  Community  We want to be in meaningful relationships with each other according to God's design. Therefore, we provide opportunities to find community through Hope Groups, church-wide gatherings, and a variety of ministry teams. "So in Christ we, though many, form one body, and each member belongs to all the others." (Romans 12:5)  On Mission Everywhere  We believe that the church exists for those outside our walls. We encourage and provide opportunities for people to BECOME On Mission Everywhere, realizing that our neighbors, coworkers, and family are our very own mission field.  Some expressions of New Hope being on mission are our Nicaragua missions, STARS tutoring ministry, Vacation Bible School, and Children of Hope Preschool. "Go and make disciples of all nations, baptizing them in the name of the Father and of the Son and of the Holy Spirit, and teaching them to obey everything I have commanded you." (Matthew 28:19-20)  To BECOME in a God-honoring way requires us to keep God at the center of all we do. Only through His presence and leading in our lives can we see our vision BECOME a reality. We desire to be a part of something so big that it is destined to fail without God. "Now to him who is able to do immeasurably more than all we ask or imagine, according to his power that is at work within us, to him be glory in the church and in Christ Jesus throughout all generations, for ever and ever! Amen." (Ephesians 3:20-21)</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/becomehope/become-biblically-equipped-community-on-mission-everywhere/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">51268a99-6b11-4e2a-bd37-284194816a58</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 19:48:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>What should I expect? What Should I Expect?  First, let us just say what we expect from you when you visit for the first time. We expect you to be yourself. We expect you to be our guest and to let us serve you. We will not expect you to be singled out, speak or pray out loud or raise a hand, give your money, sign up for the daily newsletter, sign a covenant, and honestly...you don't even have to sing real loud if you don't want to. We expect you to come and check us out, not jump in with both feet until you're sure it's a good fit.  Sundays are a great time around New Hope. Our focus is to learn more about Jesus, his plan for our lives, and how we can join his work in this world. We utilize practical teaching from the Bible and modern worship music with guitars and drums. You'll find exciting age-graded opportunities for the whole family. We have identical gatherings at both 9:00 am and 10:30 am for children and adults. (Be sure and check out the Middle School and High School pages to see what they are up to currently.) We are just a group of people on a journey to BECOME more like Jesus. We laugh a lot, we don't have it all together, but we are passionate about living out God's love.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/becomehope/what-should-i-expect-what-should-i-expect-first-let-us-j/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cbfab329-5782-4eb3-932a-91b83a16a414</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 19:47:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Times & Directions Sunday Morning  9:00am Worship Gathering in the Sanctuary (upstairs) Nursery (upstairs next to the Sanctuary) Children's Classes (downstairs)  10:30am Worship Gathering in the Sanctuary (upstairs) Nursery (upstairs next to the Sanctuary) Children's Classes (downstairs) Middle School (upstairs)  Our worship center and nursery are located upstairs and are most easily accessed through the upper parking lot. If you have kindergarten through preschool age children and would like to check them into our children's programs then the front entrance on the lower level is the best way to go. Be sure and come a few minutes early for a free cup of coffee upstairs in the cafe.     Directions  We are between Morgantown and Hwy. 37 on Fairview Rd. Driving Directions 5307 W. Fairview Rd. Greenwood, IN 46142</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://becomehope.com/~hopegree/times.php</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a86eb875-1413-48ec-88e0-7f036e5c3c72</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 19:47:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>