<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[New Hope Church - Greenwood, IN]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[New Hope Church - Greenwood, IN]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/becomehope/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 15:50:38 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/becomehope/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BECOME]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>BECOME</h1><p>Biblically Equipped Community On Mission Everywhere New Hope Church seeks to BECOME a Biblically Equipped Community On Mission Everywhere:  Biblically Equipped  We want to be in meaningful relationship with God, maturing in our faith each and every day. That is why we provide opportunities to BECOME biblically equipped through our Sunday morning teaching, Sunday adult classes, Hope Groups, age-graded ministries, and various training opportunities. "Love the Lord your God with all your heart and with all your soul and with all your mind and with all your strength." (Mark 12:30)  Community  We want to be in meaningful relationships with each other according to God's design. Therefore, we provide opportunities to find community through Hope Groups, church-wide gatherings, and a variety of ministry teams. "So in Christ we, though many, form one body, and each member belongs to all the others." (Romans 12:5)  On Mission Everywhere  We believe that the church exists for those outside our walls. We encourage and provide opportunities for people to BECOME On Mission Everywhere, realizing that our neighbors, coworkers, and family are our very own mission field.  Some expressions of New Hope being on mission are our Nicaragua missions, STARS tutoring ministry, Vacation Bible School, and Children of Hope Preschool. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/adc31ec737245768adc013ee00fde2a2b5d96c19.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://becomehope.com/~hopegree/become.php</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">51268a99-6b11-4e2a-bd37-284194816a58</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 15:45:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Times & Directions]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Times & Directions</h1><p>Sunday Morning</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://becomehope.com/~hopegree/times.php</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a86eb875-1413-48ec-88e0-7f036e5c3c72</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 15:50:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>